# **Rafael Gomes**

Junior Web Developer

#### Profile

I have been a graduate student and an avid self-learner for the past two years. I am motivated, dedicated and place value in the details. I possess an endless passion for the field and always want to further my skills and abilities.

#### Employment History

#### Sales Assistant at TK Maxx, Coleraine

October 2016 — Present

In this role i had to provide customer service, maintain areas around the store, make sure every item was in the right place and also work in the processing room and re-stock shelves. I was organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.

#### Sales Assistant at Peacocks, Portadown

June 2016 — September 2016

I was asked to provide customer service, check fitting rooms, tag all items when needed and make sure the shopping floor was kept clean and organized.

#### IT Support at Drumcree College, Portadown

January 2016 — June 2016

I worked here for my degree work experience. I was asked to do photoshopping, stock of all equipment, fixing printeres and also made a program using c# to help students that knew brief English.

#### Education

# Foundation Degree in Computer Science, Ulster University, Portadown September 2014 — June 2016

Itook a Foundation Degree at Southern Regional College in which i achieved a first overall.

#### The Complete Web Developer in 2019: Zero to Mastery, Udemy

October 2018 — January 2019

This course taught me skills that include - HTML5, CSS Grid, JS, Dom Manipulation, Command Line, Git, Github, NPM, React js, Asynchronous Javascript, APIs, and Nodejs.

#### Web Developer Bootcamp, Udemy

January 2018 — September 2018

In this course i was taught to use skills such as - HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Flexbox, JS, DOM Manipulation, JQuery, NodeJs, APIs and Git/Github.

#### ■ References

References available upon request

#### **Details**

29E Rosemary Place, Coleraine, BT522AT, Northern Ireland, 07512696231

rafaelg1402@protonmail.com

# Skills HTML CSS JavaScript React

NodeJS		

### Football, Tennis and Swimming.

<b>Languages</b> English
Portuguese

# Links

Linux

**Hobbies** 

Github